berryshare.com 2010-01-05

# BerryShare - Share Your Videos Online

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on BerryShare.com   
The security of your Data is very important to BerryShare.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.  
This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet this criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority. 

**DATA COLLECTED**

  * Personal Information: 
    * Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. No IPs are collected.
  * Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.
  * Cookies: When you visit BerryShare.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. BerryShare.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.
  * Log File Information: We do not log any private information.
  * Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

**USES**

  * Your personally identifiable information submitted to BerryShare.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalised features. 
  * Your chosen usernaname (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, at, the messages you send through the BerryShare.com private mail, etc. Other Users can contact you through, private messages. 
  * Any videos that you submit to BerryShare.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. 
  * We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We analyse aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the BerryShare.com user-experience. 

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

  * if under duty to do so BerryShare.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of BerryShare.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is BerryShare.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party. 
  * Should you deliberately upload any illegal material PormHub.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.   
\- We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

**SECURITY**  
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.   
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. BerryShare.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to BerryShare.com and you do so at your own risk. 

**YOUR RIGHTS**  
You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.BerryShare.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
www.BerryShare.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.BerryShare.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

BerryShare.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.BerryShare.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.   
  
Copyright (c) 2006-2009 BerryShare - Share Your Videos Online. All rights reserved.
